Guide to the Marilyn Horne Foundation Records, 1991-2011 CTC.2010.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Programs and Events, 1993-2011; II.
  - On Wings of Song, 1994-2010; 3.
    - 2008-2009 Season
      - Programs, 2008-2009 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - 2009-2010 Season
      - Artists and general season information, 2009-2010 (Box 89, Folder 4)
      - Programs, 2009-2010 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - The Song Continues, 1993-2011; 4.
    The Song Continues... Festival is the Marilyn Horne Foundation's annual festival that focuses on the art song. The annual festival included the gala concert, several masterclass by world-renown singers, vocal seminars, and other duo recitals by the Foundation's roster of artists. This subseries is arranged chronologically and includes files on all of the events of that festival for each given year including correspondence with the venues, marketing information, budgets, etc.
    - 1994 Festival
      - Bertelsmann Music Group agreement - Divas in Song, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 90, Folder 2)
      - Inaugural concert, 1993-1995 (Box 90, Folder 3)
      - Program, January 1994 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - 1995 Festival
      - Annual recital, 1994-1995 (Box 90, Folder 5-6)
      - Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - Program, January 1995 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - 1996 Festival
      - Annual recital, 1997 (Box 90, Folder 9)
      - Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 90, Folder 10)
      - CD/Video, 1996 (Box 90, Folder 11)
      - Invitation (Box 90, Folder 12)
      - Jaycole advertisement, 1995-1996 (Box 90, Folder 13)
      - Program, January 1996 (Box 90, Folder 14)
      - Reception, 1995-1996 (Box 90, Folder 15)
      - Schools, 1995-1996 (Box 90, Folder 16)
      - Stagebill, 1995-1996 (Box 90, Folder 17)
      - Tickets, 1995-1996 (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - Voices Across America and After Hours Productions, 1996-1997 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - 1997 Festival
      - Budget, 1996-1997 (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Thomas Hampson, 1996-1997 (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - Jaycole advertising, 1996-1997 (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - Juilliard - Artists and panel, 1996-1997 (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Juilliard - Master Class, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - Letter of agreement, 1996-1997 (Box 91, Folder 8)
      - Christa Ludwig, 1996 (Box 91, Folder 9)
      - New York Times advertisement, 1996-1997 (Box 91, Folder 10)
      - Photographs, 1997 (Box 91, Folder 11)
      - Program and three-sheet, 1996-1997 (Box 91, Folder 12)
      - Reception, 1997 (Box 91, Folder 13)
      - Tickets, 1996-1997 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - 1998 Festival
      - Advertising, 1997-1998 (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Artists, 1996-1998 (Box 92, Folder 2-3)
      - Artist waivers, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - Audio/Video, 1997-1998 (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Benefit committee, 1995-1998 (Box 92, Folder 6-7)
      - Benefit dinner, 1997 (Box 92, Folder 8)
      - Budget (Box 92, Folder 9)
      - Carnegie Hall, 1997-1998 (Box 92, Folder 10)
      - Gifts, 1994-1998 (Box 92, Folder 11)
      - Honorary benefit committee - Celebrities, 1997 (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - Honorary Chair - Mayor Rudolph Giuliani, 1997-1998 (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - Honorary Co-chair - Iris Love, 1997 (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - Honorary Co-chair - Jill Sackler (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - Invitations, 1997 (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Juilliard Theater, 1997-1998 (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - Juilliard Theater - Tickets, 1997-1998 (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - Master Class - Auditions, 1997-1998 (Box 93, Folder 8)
      - Master Class - Joan Sutherland, 1997-1998 (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - Photographer, 1997-1998 (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Posters, 1997-1998 (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Press invitations, 1997-1998 (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - Press release, August 27, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - Program and schedule, 1998 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - Reception, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - Gerard Souzay (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - Stagebill, 1994-1997 (Box 94, Folder 9)
      - Thank you notes, 1997-1998 (Box 94, Folder 10)
      - Tickets, 1997-1998 (Box 94, Folder 11)
      - Guang Yang, 1997-1998 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - 1999 Festival
      - Advertising, 1997-1998 (Box 94, Folder 13)
      - John Ardoin, 1998 (Box 94, Folder 14)
      - Artists, 1998-1999 (Box 94, Folder 15)
      - Artists waivers, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 16)
      - Benefit dinner, 1998-1999 (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Budget, 1998-2001 (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Invitations, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Juilliard Theater, 1997-1999 (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Kaplan penthouse - Birthday dinner, 1998-1999 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Master Class - Thomas Hampson, 1998-1999 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Master Class and seminar, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Karita Mattila, 1998-1999 (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence and thank yous, 1998-1999 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Program, 1998-1999 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - Promotion, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - Sponsorship, 1997-1998 (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - Tickets, 1998-1999 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - 2000 Festival
      - Advertising, 1999-2000 (Box 95, Folder 14)
      - Artists, 1999-2000 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Artist waivers, 2000 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Benefit committee, 1999-2000 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Benefit dinner - Caterer, 1999-2000 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - Benefit dinner - Gifts, 1999-2000 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - Benefit dinner - Memos and lists, 1999-2000 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Budget, 1999-2000 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - Carnegie Hall, 1999-2000 (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - Carnegie Hall - Corporate sponsorship, 1999-2000 (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - Commissions, 1999-2001 (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - Flowers, 1999-2000 (Box 96, Folder 11)
      - Follow up letters, 2000 (Box 96, Folder 12)
      - Hotel, 1999-2000 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Invitations - Doris Halle, 1999-2000 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Invoices - Ads, 1998-1999 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Juilliard Theater, 1999-2000 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Master Class - Régine Crespin, 1999-2000 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Master Classes, 1999-2000 (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Master schedule, 1999-2000 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Music Academy of the West, 1999-2000 (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Office of the Mayor's Millennium Committee - NYC 2000, 1999-2000 (Box 97, Folder 10)
      - Post-concert feedback, 2000 (Box 97, Folder 11)
      - Press invites, 1999-2000 (Box 97, Folder 12)
      - Program, 1999-2000 (Box 97, Folder 13)
      - Reviews, 2000-2001 (Box 97, Folder 14)
      - Symposium, 1999-2000 (Box 97, Folder 15)
      - Ticket returns, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 1)
      - Tickets - Carnegie, 1999-2000 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      - Tickets - Juilliard, 1999-2000 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - 2001 Festival
      - Advertising, 2000-2001 (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - Advertising program, 2000-2001 (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - Artists' waivers, 2000 (Box 98, Folder 6)
      - Artists - Hotels, 2000-2001 (Box 98, Folder 7)
      - Benefit dinner, 2000-2001 (Box 98, Folder 8)
      - Benefit dinner - Gifts, 1997-2001 (Box 98, Folder 9)
      - Budget, 2000-2001 (Box 98, Folder 10)
      - Caterer, 2000-2001 (Box 98, Folder 11)
      - Commission - Libby Larsen, 2000-2001 (Box 98, Folder 12)
      - Hans Hotter, 2000-2001 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - Invitations (Box 99, Folder 2)
      - Invitations - Juilliard, 2000-2001 (Box 99, Folder 3)
      - Kaplan penthouse, 2000-2001 (Box 99, Folder 4)
      - Master Class - James Levine, 2000-2001 (Box 99, Folder 5)
      - Master Class - Schedule, 2000-2001 (Box 99, Folder 6)
      - Master Class - Shirley Verrett, 2000-2001 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      - Master Classes, 2000-2001 (Box 99, Folder 8-9)
      - Program, 2000-2001 (Box 99, Folder 10)
      - Program - Advertisements (Box 99, Folder 11)
      - Tickets, 2000-2001 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - 2002 Festival
      - Advertising, 2001-2002 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Artists, 2001-2002 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Artist waivers, 2002 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Benefit dinner, 2001 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Benefit dinner - Gifts, 2001-2002 (Box 100, Folder 5)
      - Budget, 2001-2002 (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Caterer, 2001-2002 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - Marvin Hamlisch, 2001-2002 (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - Hotel, 2001 (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - Invitations, 2000-2002 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - Juilliard Theater, 2001-2002 (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - Kaplan penthouse, 2000-2001 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Master Class - Phyllis Curtin, 2002 (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - Master Classes, 2001-2002 (Box 101, Folder 7-8)
      - Photography, 2001-2002 (Box 101, Folder 9)
      - Program, 2001-2002 (Box 101, Folder 10)
      - Schedule, 2001-2002 (Box 101, Folder 11)
      - Supertitles, 2000-2002 (Box 101, Folder 12)
      - Supertitles survey, January 18, 2002 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - Tickets - Master Class and recital, 2001-2002 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - 2003 Festival
      - Advertising, 2002-2003 (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - Artists, 2002-2003 (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - Artist waivers, 2003 (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - Benefit dinner, 2002-2003 (Box 102, Folder 6-7)
      - Benefit dinner - Gifts, 2002-2003 (Box 102, Folder 8)
      - Budget, 2002-2004 (Box 102, Folder 9-10)
      - Caterer, 2002-2003 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - Invitations, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - Juilliard Theater, 2002-2003 (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - Master Class - Auditions, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - Master Class - Grace Bumbry, 2002-2003 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - Master Classes, 2002-2003 (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - Master schedule, 2002-2003 (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - Photography, 2002-2003 (Box 103, Folder 8)
      - Program, January 2003 (Box 103, Folder 9-10)
      - Recital program, 2002 (Box 103, Folder 11)
      - Tickets, 2001-2003 (Box 104, Folder 1-2)
      - Underwriting, 2000-2003 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - 2004 Festival
      - Advertising, 2003-2004 (Box 104, Folder 4)
      - Archival tapes - Audio and Video, 2003-2004 (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - Artist waivers, 2004 (Box 104, Folder 6)
      - Artists, 2003-2004 (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - Artists - Audra McDonald, 2003-2004 (Box 104, Folder 8)
      - Artists - Bejun Metha, 2003-2004 (Box 104, Folder 9)
      - Artists - Ben Heppner, 2003-2004 (Box 104, Folder 10)
      - Artists - Brian Stokes Mitchell, 2003-2004 (Box 104, Folder 11)
      - Artists - Denyce Graves, 2003-2004 (Box 104, Folder 12)
      - Artists - Duo recitals, 2003-2004 (Box 104, Folder 13)
      - Artists - Frederica Von Stade, 2003-2004 (Box 104, Folder 14)
      - Artists - Isabel Bayrakdarian, 2003-2004 (Box 104, Folder 15)
      - Artists - Lang Lang, 2002-2004 (Box 104, Folder 16)
      - Artists - Martin Katz, 2003-2004 (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - Artists - Marvin Hamlisch, 2003-2004 (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Artists - Olga Borodina, 2003-2004 (Box 105, Folder 3)
      - Artists - Stephanie Blythe, 2003-2004 (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - Artists - Thomas Quasthoff, 2003-2004 (Box 105, Folder 5)
      - Artists - Twyla Robinson, 2003-2004 (Box 105, Folder 6)
      - Benefit committee, 2003-2004 (Box 105, Folder 7)
      - Benefit dinner - Caterer, 2003-2004 (Box 105, Folder 8)
      - Benefit dinner - Gifts, 2003-2004 (Box 105, Folder 9)
      - Benefit dinner - Table seating, 2003-2004 (Box 105, Folder 10)
      - Breakfast with the Arts - A&E network, 2003 (Box 105, Folder 11)
      - Budget, 2003-2004 (Box 105, Folder 12-13)
      - Carnegie Hall, 2002-2004 (Box 106, Folder 1-2)
      - Carnegie Talk event, 2003 (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - Clintons, 1994-2004 (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - Commemorative program, 2002-2003 (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - Commemorative program - Draft, 2003 (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - Commission, 2003-2004 (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - Congratulations, 2004 (Box 106, Folder 8)
      - David Daniels, 2003-2004 (Box 106, Folder 9)
      - Essex House, 2003-2004 (Box 106, Folder 10)
      - Flowers, 2003-2004 (Box 106, Folder 11)
      - Follow up letters, 2003-2004 (Box 106, Folder 12)
      - Invitations, 2003-2004 (Box 107, Folder 1)
      - Master Class - Deborah Voigt, 2003-2004 (Box 107, Folder 2)
      - Master Class - Reimbursements, 2003-2004 (Box 107, Folder 3)
      - Master Class - Seminar (Box 107, Folder 4)
      - Master Class - Thomas Hampson, 2003-2004 (Box 107, Folder 5)
      - Master Classes, 2003 (Box 107, Folder 6)
      - Photography, 2003-2004 (Box 108, Folder 1)
      - Program, 2003-2004 (Box 108, Folder 2-5)
      - Program - Advertising, 2003-2004 (Box 108, Folder 6)
      - Rehearsal, 2003-2004 (Box 108, Folder 7)
      - Roundtable, 2003-2004 (Box 108, Folder 8)
      - Student - Complimentary tickets, 2003 (Box 108, Folder 9)
      - Supertitles, 2003-2004 (Box 108, Folder 10)
      - Tickets, 2003 (Box 108, Folder 11)
      - Video, 2003-2004 (Box 108, Folder 12)
      - Wellington Hotel, 2003-2004 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - 2005 Festival
      - Advertising, 2004-2005 (Box 109, Folder 1)
      - Artists, 2004-2005 (Box 109, Folder 2)
      - Artist waivers, 2005 (Box 109, Folder 3)
      - Auction, 2005-2006 (Box 109, Folder 4)
      - Auction prizes, 2004-2005 (Box 109, Folder 5)
      - Benefit dinner, 2003-2005 (Box 109, Folder 6-7)
      - Budget, 2004-2006 (Box 110, Folder 1-2)
      - Carnegie Hall, 2003-2005 (Box 110, Folder 3)
      - Commission - John Musto, 2004-2005 (Box 110, Folder 4)
      - Duo recital - Deborah Domansky / William Jason Hardy, 2004-2005 (Box 110, Folder 5)
      - Duo recital - Jessica Jones/ Weston Hurt, 2004 (Box 110, Folder 6)
      - Feedback, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 7)
      - Invitations, 2004-2005 (Box 110, Folder 8-9)
      - Master Class - Auditions, 2004-2005 (Box 110, Folder 10)
      - Master Class - Benita Valente, 2004 (Box 110, Folder 11)
      - Master Class - James Levine, 2004-2005 (Box 110, Folder 12)
      - Master Class - Marilyn Horne, 2003-2004 (Box 110, Folder 13)
      - René Pape, 2004-2005 (Box 110, Folder 14)
      - Photography, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 15)
      - Program, 2005 (Box 111, Folder 1)
      - Tickets, 2004-2005 (Box 111, Folder 2-3)
    - 2006 Festival
      - Advertising, 2004-2006 (Box 111, Folder 4)
      - Annual Recital, 2005-2006 (Box 111, Folder 5)
      - Artist waivers, 2006 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      - Auction, 2005-2006 (Box 111, Folder 7)
      - Benefit dinner, 2005-2006 (Box 111, Folder 8)
      - Benefit dinner - Advertisements, 2005-2006 (Box 111, Folder 9)
      - Buckingham Hall rooms, 2005-2006 (Box 112, Folder 1)
      - Budget, 2005-2006 (Box 112, Folder 2-3)
      - Carnegie Hall, 2005-2006 (Box 112, Folder 4)
      - Commission - Ben Moore, 2005-2006 (Box 112, Folder 5)
      - Duo recitals, 2005-2006 (Box 112, Folder 6)
      - Hotel rooms, 2005-2006 (Box 112, Folder 7)
      - Invitations, 2005-2006 (Box 112, Folder 8)
      - Master Class - Auditions, 2004-2005 (Box 112, Folder 9)
      - Master Classes, 2005-2006 (Box 112, Folder 10)
      - Master Class - Frank Corsaro, 2005-2006 (Box 113, Folder 1)
      - Photography, 2005-2006 (Box 113, Folder 2)
      - Programs, January 2006 (Box 113, Folder 3-4)
      - Schedule, 2006 (Box 113, Folder 5)
      - Tickets, 2005-2006 (Box 113, Folder 6-9)
      - Travel and accommodations, 2005-2006 (Box 113, Folder 10)
      - Frederica Von Stade, 2005-2006 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - 2007 Festival
      - Advertising, 2006-2007 (Box 113, Folder 12)
      - Annual recital, 2006-2007 (Box 113, Folder 13)
      - Artist waivers, 2007 (Box 113, Folder 14)
      - Auction, 2005-2007 (Box 113, Folder 15)
      - Benefit committee - Co-chairs, 2006-2007 (Box 113, Folder 16)
      - Benefit dinner, 2006-2007 (Box 113, Folder 17)
      - Buckingham Hotel, 2006-2007 (Box 113, Folder 18)
      - Budget, 2006-2007 (Box 114, Folder 1-2)
      - Carnegie Hall, 2004-2007 (Box 114, Folder 3)
      - Commission - Gabriela Lena Frank, 2006-2007 (Box 114, Folder 4)
      - Duo recitals, 2006-2007 (Box 115, Folder 1)
      - Marcello Giordani, 2005-2007 (Box 115, Folder 2)
      - Master Class - Barbara Cook, 2006-2007 (Box 115, Folder 3)
      - Master Class - Evelyn Lear, 2006-2007 (Box 115, Folder 4)
      - Master Class - Marilyn Horne, 2006-2007 (Box 115, Folder 5)
      - Photography, 2007 (Box 115, Folder 6)
      - Programs, January 2007 (Box 115, Folder 7)
      - Souvenir program - Advertisements, 2006-2007 (Box 115, Folder 8)
      - Recital music, 2006 (Box 115, Folder 9-10)
      - Schedule, 2005-2007 (Box 116, Folder 1)
      - Tickets, 2006-2007 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - 2008 Festival
      - Advertising, 2008 (Box 116, Folder 3)
      - Artists, 2005-2008 (Box 116, Folder 4)
      - Auction, 2007-2008 (Box 116, Folder 5-6)
      - Benefit committee lists, 2007 (Box 116, Folder 7)
      - Benefit dinner, 2007-2008 (Box 116, Folder 8)
      - Buckingham Hotel, 2007-2008 (Box 116, Folder 9)
      - Budget, 2007-2008 (Box 116, Folder 10-11)
      - Carnegie Hall, 2007 (Box 116, Folder 12)
      - Carnegie Hall - Media kit, 2007-2008 (Box 116, Folder 13)
      - Commission - Scott Wheeler, 2007-2008 (Box 117, Folder 1)
      - Duo recitals, 2007-2008 (Box 117, Folder 2)
      - Flowers, 2008 (Box 117, Folder 3)
      - Invitations, 2007 (Box 117, Folder 4)
      - Master Class - Marilyn Horne (Box 117, Folder 5)
      - Master Class - Graham Johnson, 2007-2008 (Box 117, Folder 6)
      - Master Class - Dawn Upshaw, 2007-2008 (Box 117, Folder 7)
      - Programs, January 2008 (Box 117, Folder 8)
      - Tickets, 2007-2008 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - 2009 Festival
      - Advertising, 2009 (Box 117, Folder 10-11)
      - Annual recital - Co-chairs, 2007-2008 (Box 117, Folder 12)
      - Artistic planning committee, 2007-2009 (Box 117, Folder 13)
      - Artists - Gifts, 2008-2009 (Box 117, Folder 14)
      - Artists - Planning, 2005-2009 (Box 117, Folder 15)
      - Artists - Travel and hotel, 2008-2009 (Box 118, Folder 1)
      - Artists - Waivers, January 2009 (Box 118, Folder 2)
      - Benefit committee, 2008 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      - Benefit dinner, 2008-2009 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      - Benefit dinner - Plaza Hotel, 2007-2009 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      - Benefit dinner - Gifts, 2008 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      - Buckingham Hotel, 2008-2009 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      - Budget, 2008-2009 (Box 118, Folder 8-10)
      - Carnegie Hall, 2007-2008 (Box 118, Folder 11-12)
      - Commission - William Bolcom, 2007-2008 (Box 119, Folder 1)
      - Commission - Richard Hundley, 2008 (Box 119, Folder 2)
      - Duo recitals, 2007-2009 (Box 119, Folder 3)
      - Executive planning committee, 2004-2008 (Box 119, Folder 4)
      - Feedback, 2008-2009 (Box 119, Folder 5)
      - Honorary artists committee, 2007-2008 (Box 119, Folder 6)
      - Invitation, 2008 (Box 119, Folder 7)
      - Marilyn and Friends event, 2008-2009 (Box 119, Folder 8)
      - Master Class - James Levine (Box 119, Folder 9)
      - Master Class - Marilyn Horne, 2008 (Box 119, Folder 10)
      - Master Class - Martin Katz, 2008 (Box 119, Folder 11)
      - Master Class - Schedule, 2007-2009 (Box 119, Folder 12)
      - Photography, 2008-2009 (Box 119, Folder 13)
      - Programs, 2009 (Box 119, Folder 14)
      - Schedule, 2008 (Box 119, Folder 15)
      - Sponsorship, 2007-2008 (Box 120, Folder 1)
      - Telecast on WNET, 2007-2009 (Box 120, Folder 2)
      - Tickets, 2006-2009 (Box 120, Folder 3-4)
      - Video tribute, 2007-2008 (Box 120, Folder 5-7)
    - 2010 Festival
      - Advertising, 2009-2010 (Box 120, Folder 8)
      - Annual recital, 2009-2010 (Box 121, Folder 1)
      - Benefit dinner, 2009-2010 (Box 121, Folder 2)
      - Budget (Box 121, Folder 3)
      - Carnegie Hall, 2009-2010 (Box 121, Folder 4)
      - Commission - John Musto, 2009 (Box 121, Folder 5)
      - Duo recitals, 2009-2010 (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - Master Class - James Levine, 2009-2010 (Box 121, Folder 7)
      - Programs, January 2010 (Box 121, Folder 8)
      - Tickets, 2009-2010 (Box 121, Folder 9-10)
    - 2011 Festival
      - Programs, January 2011 (Box 121, Folder 11)
- Photographs, 1994-2009; III.
  This series contains photographs of the Marilyn Horne Foundation's concerts, recitals, receptions, and benefits. The materials are arranged into three different subseries - On Wings of Song, the Song Continues, and Benefits and the National Residency program. The Benefits and the National Residency program photos are arranged alphabettically while the other two subseries are arranged chronologically.
  - Benefits, National Residency Program, and other photos, 1994-2009; 1.
    This subseries of photographs is arranged alphabetically by title. It includes photos from the Marilyn Horne Foundation's national residency performances accros the US, photos from benefit events, and other photographs related to the Foundation.
    - Benefit dinner - Essex House, January 16, 1998 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Benefit dinner - Essex House, January 16, 2000 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Benefit dinner - Essex House, January 26, 2007 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Benefit dinner - Grand Ballroom at the Plaza, January 18, 2009 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Benefit dinner - Kaplan penthouse, January 15, 1999 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Benefit dinner - Kaplan penthouse, January 18, 2002 (Box 122, Folder 6-7)
    - Benefit dinner - School of American Ballet, January 17, 2003 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Bognar dinner, April 18, 2001 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Brownville Concert Series - Deborah Domanski, November 23, 2003 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Brownville Concert Series - Alex Richardson, September 18, 2006 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Children's concert, May 2006 (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - Composers and Commissions (Box 122, Folder 13)
    - Donors - Receptions, 1998-2003 (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - *Education programs - New York City (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Fund raiser - San Francisco and Hillsborough, September 24, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 2-3)
    - LaGuardia High School, April 1, 2009 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Marilyn Horne Foundation offices, 2005 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Marilyn Horne 70th birthday receptions in California, November 2003 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Marilyn Horne with Florence Henderson and Carol Burnett (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous receptions and office photos, 2000-2003 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Music Academy of the West, 1997 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Music Academy of the West, 2007 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - National residency program, 1999-2006 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - National residency program, 1999-2006 (Box 124, Folder 1-3)
    - *New York City Education programs, June 2002 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Oberlin Conservatory residency - Lydia Brown and Nicholas Phan, February 2009 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Open House at Horne Foundation offices, May 2004 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Reception - Home of Jill Sachler, November 5, 1997 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Saint Paul Sunday radio session, September 17, 2006 (Box 124, Folder 8-9)
    - Southeastern Louisiana University residency - Andrew Garland, October 2005 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Sony Corporation event, October 3, 1999 (Box 124, Folder 11-12)
    - Supertitles, December 2002 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - William Ferguson (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Workshops, April 2004 (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - On Wings of Song, 1996-2007; 2.
    On Wings of Song is the Marilyn Horne Foundation's monthly vocal recital program which features young artists. This subseries of photographs is arranged chronologically.
    - On Wings of Song, 1996-2002 (Box 125, Folder 1-8)
    - On Wings of Song, 2002-2003 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - On Wings of Song, 2003-2004 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - On Wings of Song - William Ferguson, May 16, 2004 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - On Wings of Song, 2005-2006 (Box 126, Folder 4)